Shearing it so you have this
whole circulation, but it is
tropical storm force. We‘ll look
at that at the end
see the giant ridge in the west
and it‘s just going to move over
the weekend over us suppressing
further west, and then by Monday
it jogs just a little bit to the
east, and that opens up the
So we do have that front keeping
it cool east of the Rockies on
Thursday that
pushes away and then Saturday
there are blobs in places
including up in Northeast
Colorado
pretty good all right let‘s look
at precipitable water it is just
very rich
But the ridge is going to
suppress, a high pressure center
is going to suppress convection
there and some of that moisture
is bertha actually coming up to
Arizona but
and yeah it just stays very
August initially I can kick off
some good thunderstorms we‘ll
see that
Then to Friday and Saturday we
drop
forties and thirties so that
also makes it hard to get good
thunderstorms but by
good moisture starts coming back
again and there you got some
yellows with the
and 62 points by midweek so yeah
lots of good thunderstorm fuel
that is really